Hello Beauties, today we are going to do the
real review of Very Miss Foundation. You all have seen
its ads on
Instagram saying that you want to try new things,
so I
ordered a full box of it. If you order just the foundation, it costs Rs.
250. There is no paid promotional video.
I got the
entire thing for Rs. 650, which includes a
foundation. I
ordered the number one shade for Compactlogics.
And we will see how this foundation is. It claims to
hide all the blemishes, so
we will apply it and see what effect
it has on my face. I already see
how many marks I have, let's see if it can cover them
or not. First of all, we will apply the
primer. On top of that, I will apply the primer. First,
I am applying the
primer that came with it, it is a silicone base
primer. And for a smooth application, I have
taken a little primer and I have applied it. It is a
Natural Glow and Daily Base Foundation.
Shake it well.
Its applicator is something like this.
Earlier, it used to come in old foundations,
I used this in Lakme etc. And now I am
applying it with the help of my brush. Here's what it has.
I am showing you the application at half pace. The
application is really very smooth and
you can see the difference between the
condition of the face here and how smooth it has become.
I have applied it properly on both the sides. The
foundation has light coverage. It is for
daily use. It is a good foundation. It
feels very light on the face. It does
not require much effort. It is
blending smoothly. You can
do it with the help of a brush or with your fingers.
Just a little applicator and a little bit like
today's method. It would have been better.
See, this is the look of the foundation.
I applied a little lipstick and a little blush.
After that, you can build up this foundation.
Not very well, but
this foundation is very good for daily use. You
can purchase it. This is not a paid promotional
video. It is a genuine review. If
you liked it, then like, share
and do share it with your family and friends.
Take care of
yourself. By Beauty